Joey Bishop papers
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Projects.
  - the Glen Campbell Goodtime Hour - first draft script and binder., 1971 Feb 9. (Box 45)
  - Jimmy Durante Presents The Lennon Sisters Hour - final draft script and binder., 1969 July 10. (Box 45)
  - Rowan and Martin's Laugh-In - second draft script and binder., 1970 Dec 4. (Box 45)
  - Rowan and Martin's Laugh-In - second draft script, head shots and binder., 1968 Feb 22. (Box 45)
  - The Seven Year Itch - script., undated. (Box 45)
  - The Sonny and Cher Show - first draft script and binder., 1971 Dec 11. (Box 45)